35awards.com 2018-06-07

# International photo contest 2017 - 100 BEST PHOTOS of the year

35AWARDS is founded on the principle of helping people discover new photos and photographers. 

This Privacy Policy covers 35AWARDS treatment of personal information that 35AWARDS.com gathers when you are on the 35AWARDS.com website and when you use 35AWARDS services. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that 35AWARDS does not own or control, or to individuals that 35AWARDS does not employ or manage.

The rights to all images on this site are those of the authors of these photos. 

We collect information in two ways:

1\. When you give it to us or give us permission to obtain it. When you sign up for or use our services, you voluntarily give us certain information. This can include your name, profile photo, posts, comments, email address you used to sign up, and any other information you provide us. If you're using 35AWARDS on your mobile device, you can also choose to provide us with location data.

You also may give us permission to access your information in other services. For example, you may link your Facebook or Vkontakte account to 35AWARDS, which allows us to obtain information from those accounts (e.g., your friends or contacts). The information we obtain from those services often depends on your settings or their privacy policies, so be sure to check what those are.

2\. We get technical information when you use our services. For most websites, mobile applications, or other Internet services, there's certain information that almost always gets created and recorded automatically. This is true when you use our services, and here are some of the types of information we collect in this way.

Log Data. When you use 35AWARDS, our servers automatically record information about your interaction with our services ("log data"), including information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website or your mobile app sends when you use it to access 35AWARDS. This log data may include your Internet Protocol address, the address of the web page you were visiting before you came to 35AWARDS, browser type and settings, the date and time of your request, and how you used 35AWARDS.

Depending on how you're accessing our products, we may use "cookies" (a small text file sent by your computer each time you visit our website, unique to your 35AWARDS account or your browser), or similar technologies to record log data. When we use cookies, we may use "session" cookies (that last until you close your browser) or "persistent" cookies (that last until you or your browser delete them). For example, we may use cookies to store your language preferences or other 35AWARDS settings so you don't have to set them up every time you visit 35AWARDS.

Device Information. In addition to log data, we may also collect information about the device you're using 35AWARDS on, including what type of device it is, what operating system you're using, device settings, unique device identifiers, and crash data. Whether we collect some or all of this information often depends on what type of device you're using and its settings. For example, different types of information are available depending on whether you're using a Mac or a PC, or an iPhone or an Android phone. To learn more about what information your device makes available to us, please also check the policies of your device manufacturer or software provider.

How do we use the information we collect?

We use the information we collect to provide our services to you and make them better, develop new services and products, and protect 35AWARDS and our users. For example, we may log how often people use two different versions of a service, which can help us understand which version is better.

We also use the information we collect to offer you customized content -- including helping you discover posts, topics, or other users you might find interesting, or provide you with tailored advertising.

We also use the information we collect to:

Send you updates (such as when your posts or comments on 35AWARDS are liked or shared by others), newsletters, marketing materials and other information that may be of interest to you. For example, depending on your email notification settings, we may send you weekly updates that include articles you may like. You can decide to stop getting these updates by updating your account settings (or through other settings we may provide). The information we collect may be "personally identifiable" (meaning it can be used to specifically identify you as a unique person) or "non-personally identifiable" (meaning it can't be used to specifically identify you). We use both types of information, and combinations of both types, as described above. We may use or store information wherever 35AWARDS does business, including countries outside your own.

What choices do you have about your information?

Our goal is to give you simple and meaningful choices over your information. If you have a 35AWARDS account, many of the choices you have on 35AWARDS are built directly in to the services or your account settings. For example, you can:

Access and change information in your profile page at any time, and choose whether your profile page is available to search engines; Link or unlink your 35AWARDS account from an account on another service (e.g., Facebook or Twitter). For some services (like Facebook), you can also choose whether or not to publish your activity on 35AWARDS to that service. Close your account at any time. When you close your account, we'll deactivate it and remove your posts from 35AWARDS. We may retain archived copies of your information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes (including to help address fraud and spam).

You may have choices available to you through the device or software you use to access 35AWARDS. For example:

The browser you use may provide you with the ability to control cookies or other types of local data storage; Your mobile device may provide you with choices around how and whether location or other data is shared with us. To learn more about these choices, please see the information provided by the device or software provider.

What information do we collect?

35AWARDS is a tool people use to find inspiration, make inspirations a reality, and inspire others in the process. When you create public profiles, portfolios and posts, anyone can view them. The other limited instances where we may share your personal information include:

When we have your consent. This includes sharing information with other services (like Facebook or Twitter) when you’ve chosen to link to your 35AWARDS account to those services or publish your activity on 35AWARDS to them. For example, you can choose to publish your posts to Facebook or Twitter. We may employ third party companies or individuals to process personal information on our behalf based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy. For example, we may share data with a security consultant to help us get better at identifying spam or with our accountants to make sure we’re keeping the books right. In addition, some of the information we request may be collected by third party providers on our behalf. If we believe that disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety, rights, or property of the public, any person, or 35AWARDS; or to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues. We may engage in a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, reorganization, or similar transaction or proceeding that involves the transfer of the information described in this Policy. We may also share aggregated or non-personally identifiable information with our partners or others.

How do we make changes to this policy?

We may change this policy from time to time, and if we do we’ll post any changes on this page. If you continue to use 35AWARDS after those changes are in effect, you agree to the revised policy. If the changes are significant, we may provide more prominent notice or obtain your consent as required by law.
